# Hao Wu

**User Experience Designer** 

hermia.haow@gmail.com 416-871-3063 linkedin.com/in/hermia-wu/ github.com/hermiawu

#### **PROFILE**

I am a passionate designer, who is excited to be beginning a career in UX.

Being keen on studying human behaviours, I have spent about 5 years researching how humans access the physical space and how they deal with numbers, especially financial behaviors. When it comes to the digital world. HCI is the field where I would ideally like to work in. I would love to use my interdisciplinary skills of architectural design and financial research to create digital solutions that are not only charmful but also going to make users' life better.

#### **SKILLS**

Sketching/Wireframing/Protot yping (Figma, Sketch, Invision, POP App, Principle, Protopie) Graphic Design( Photoshop, Illustrator, Indesign, Premiere, After Effects), Java, Javascript, HTMLI, CSS, jQuery, Project Management (Trello, Asana)

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Graphic/UI Designer | Self-Employed

MAR 2020 - PRESENT, TORONTO, ON

- Redesigned UI from inception to final product and successfully launched brand new McMaster Sumobot Competition website (<u>sumobot.ca</u>) which increased visitors by 50%
- Developed high-quality mock-ups and UI for 2 mobile apps

## Junior Architectural Designer | Oleson Worland Architects

DEC 2019 - PRESENT, TORONTO, ON

- Implemented innovative conceptual design sketches, and models for review by design software, like Adobe Suite and AutoCAD
- Established and maintained collaborative relationships with involved parties, including City Hall, clients, other designers and engineers
- Refined company's workflow, which increased the efficiency by 30%

#### **EDUCATION**

## **BrainStation** | Diploma Candidate, User Experience Design

AUG - OCT 2020, TORONTO, ON

# University of Toronto | Bachelor of Arts, Architectural Studies

SEP 2016 - 2019, TORONTO, ON

Daniels Undergraduate Technology Award. Graduate with High Distinction. Dean's List Scholar

#### **PROJECTS**

# Hm.So.. - Home Social App | Lead UX Designer, Researcher

AUG 2020 - PRESENT, HACKATHON (HACK THE 6IX)

- Home-based social app that mainly helps people express themselves properly to improve their relationship with roommates
- Coordinated the project and collaborated with developers to realize text to emoji transformation (NLP), public space management, and activity status animation within 36 hrs

## <u>Pre.Module</u> - Prefabricated Building App | Full-Stack UX Designer

AUG 2020 - PRESENT, BrainStation Capstone

- To educate and encourage young professionals to access prefabricated buildings in order to reduce their rental financial pressure
- Took the role of a whole-process UX designer, creating this case study from research, to ideation and realization, and to the stage of multi-platform marketing